pickup backpack
put down backpack
turn on oven
pickup kettle
pour out kettle
fill up kettle
put down kettle
turn on kettle
pick up frying pan
put down frying pan
pick up colander
pick up pots
put down pots
rearrange pots
pick up pot
fill pot with water
Put pot on stove
Open fridge
Take out courgette
Move cheese
Open courgette
Empty courgette into sink
Throw away plastic
Turn on tap
Rinse courgette
Pick up courgette
Shake off courgette
Put down courgette
Open cupboard
Take out olive oil
Pour olive oil in pan
Put on lid
Put on olive oil lid
Put down olive oil
Put away phone
Pick up slicer
Pick up courgette
Slice courgette into bin
Slice courgette into pan
slice
courgette into pan
throw away courgette
slice courgette into bin
slice courgette into pan
throw away courgette
slice courgette into bin
slice courgette into pan
shake courgette
pick up spatula
stir courgette
pick up courgette
slice courgette into bin
slice courgette into pan
throw away courgette
pick up onion
pick up chopping block
put down onion
pick up knife
slice onion
drop onion
remove onion skin
throw away onion skin
stir courgette
slice open onions
remove onion
drop onion
put down onion
throw away onion bag
pick up onions
put down onion
remove onion skin
choose onion
cut top off onion
cut bottom off onion
remove onion skin
throw away onion skin
stir courgette
cut onion in half
remove onion skin
slice onions
slice onion
pick up knife
collect onion skins
throw away onion skins
move madoline slicer
pick up onions
chop onions
clean off knife
spill onions
pour onions into pan
stir courgettes
adjust oven
turn on water to boil
pour water into pot
put down kettle
rearrange pans
pickup lids
put lid on pot
stir courgette
stir onions
Stir onions
Turn on tap
Rinse hands
Dry off hands
Open window
Stir courgette
Remove courgette
Stir onions
Adjust oven
Swap pans
Open cupboards
Take out pasta
Take out measuring jug
measure pasta
put away pasta
pick up measuring jug
take off lid
pour pasta into pot
put lid back on
open cupboards
put away measuring jug
put away pasta
close cupboards
set oven timer
stir onions
swap pans
stir courgette
adjust hob
open fridge
take out cheese
take out artichokes
take out sun-dried tomato
open artichokes
get fork
open olives
remove olives
take lid off pasta
stir courgette
stir onions
adjust hub
stir courgette
remove olives
close olives
put olives in fridge
open artichokes
remove artichokes
put artichokes in fridge
open sun dried tomatoes
stir courgette
Stir onions
Put lid on pasta
Clean off fork
Remove sun dried tomatoes
Remove sun dried tomato
Take lid off pasta
Stir onions
Stir courgette
stir courgette
adjust oven
put with unsundried tomatoes
put away sundried tomatoes
pick up fork
put fork in sink
pick up guards
pick up slicer
put slicer on side
pick up knife
rearrange tomatoes
pick up cheese
empty cheese
throw away cheese wrapper
move olives
move sun-dried tomatoes
chop sun-dried tomatoes
clean off knife
put down knife
check timer
adjust hob
stir courgette
stir onions
chop artichokes
chop olives
chop olives and artichokes
chop cheese
clean off knife
stir courgette
adjust hobs
stir onions
adjust lid
turn on taps
rinse hands
pour soap on hands
clean fork
clean guard
clean slicer
scrub slicer
turn on tap
rinse slicer
put away slicer
rinse fork
put away fork
rinse guard
turn off tap
drop guard
rinse guard
put away guard
adjust lid
stir courgettes
adjust hob
pick up courgettes
Eat courgette
Chew on courgette
Adjust hob
Stir courgette
Stir onions
Turn off timer
Pick up colander
Put back pot
Put colander in sink
Pick up pot
Pour pot in colander
Put pot on lid
Pick up colander
put down pot
put down pot on hub
put caulder on pot
put lid in sink
stirrings
pick up chopping block
put artichokes in pan
put down knife
chopping block
put cheese in pan
clean off knife
scrape cheese into pan
scrape cheese
clean off knife
put down chopping blocking knife
pick up pasta
pour pasta into pan
put down calonder
stir courgette
pick up olive oil
put olive oil on courgette
stir courgette
Stir pasta
Put away Tupperware
Rinse knife
Clean knife
Rinse off knife
Put away knife
Pick up chopping block
Rinse off chopping block
Scrub chopping block
Rinse hands
Adjust hob
start courgettes
start courgette
pour pasta onto courgettes
adjust hub
pickup lids
pour soap on lids
scrub lids
scrub lid
grab lid
rinse off lid
put lid into drying rack
empty sink
pour soap on chopping block
scrub chopping block
Rinse hands
Rinse chopping block
Put away chopping block
Pick up pan
Stir pan
Rinse pan
Pour soap in pan
Scrub pan
Rinse off
pan
Rinse off pan
Put pan on hob
Pickup colander
Pickup pan
Rinse pan
Scrub pan
Rinse off pan
Put away pan
Pickup colander
Rinse colander
Scrub colander
rinse colander
put away colander
dry hands
open cupboards
take out bowls
close cupboards
put down bowls
pick up tissue
wipe down surface
throw away tissue
pick up bowls
rearrange bowl
open cupboards
put away olive oil
pour food in bowl
put pan in sink
turn on tap
rise hands
rinse spatula
scrub spatula
pour soap in pan
scrub pan
scrub spatula
rinse spatula
put away spatula
rinse pan
scrub pan
scrub
pan
Scrub pan
Rinse sponge
Rinse hands
Rinse
pan
Rinse pan
Scrub back of pan
Put pan on hob
Pick up fork
Put fork in bowls